With pop and a step and I've gotcha!
Let's put on another flashy performance today-pri!
Meganii?!
A patrolling Meganii?!
Is this really the time to be goofing off?
I'm not goofing off.
It looks like you are to me-pri.
This time, I stole your heart.
Autumn is just around the corner.
Phantom Thief Genius said he'd be back this autumn!
Get out there and catch him so I
don't have to worry about winning!
I've already devised a plan to deal with him.
That's why I'm patrolling like this.
And on top of that, I've put in a request
to the Parajuku PriPara Police...
to dispatch the PriPara Police!
The "PriPara Police"?
Ham and Ajimi.
Our police force is top-notch,
so there's nothing to worry about.
And with that, I'll return to patrolling.
The PriPara Police, huh?
I wonder what kind of people will show up?
Candy À La Mode has a new brand for
the artist who loves painting pictures.
The cute poppin' Candy À La Mode More fits her perfectly!
PriPara change grecomplete!
Da Vinci!
Wha?
Sh-She sure looked like a cute idol...
It's like color in full bloom.
Her coord is full of color.
I've never seen her before-pri.
You think maybe she's one of the PriPara Police?
I'm not so sure about that one...
She's got to be!
Within minutes of Meganii calling the police,
a new idol appeared.
You can't prove me wrong!
You could be right.
She might be with the police-pri...
You look picture Picasso perfect!
Let's have some fun-da Vinci!
There's no way-pri.
What the heck did she say?
Play?
Wah!
Yehello there!
I'm Kiki Ajimi!
I'm making my PriPara debut today-da Vinci!
N-Nice to capisce ya.
Hey now!
Laala's face isn't your sketchbook-pri.
Wha?!
What the heck are you doing?!
Everybody's shiny-shiny, frilly-frilly, sparkly-sparkly...
and cute-da Vinci!
Autumn is the season of art!
I'm full of so Munch Klimt creativity-da Vinci.
I don't think she's listening.
She sure hasn't heard of personal space.
And hey, don't graffiti all over the walls-pri!
Heart jumping dancing-da Vinci!
Sh-She's using wordplays and enders,
so I guess that means she's a punny kind of idol-pri.
She uses too many.
I can't begin to figure out what she's prattling about.
This is worse than Mirei's "pri".
It sounds like she's using artist's names-pri.
Picasso, Da Vinci...
Since she's an artist, I guess she
ends her sentences with "da Vinci"?
Who the Vinci is Da Vinci?
What do you mean "who the Vinci"-pri!
Da Vinci as in the Leonardo from the village Vinci.
You know, Leonardo da Vinci.
To put it simply, a famous historical artist-pri.
Oh? I see...
Da Vinci.
Ta-da!
Michelange-look!
Take a Venus de Mi-look!
Complete-da Vinci!
Capisce!
It's adorable!
She brought out my cute side!
How ceatively original.
A thunderous applause to you.
Look at the sunflowers!
I can feel the Winds of Andalucia-pri.
It's embarrassing to have you praise me deske-like that!
My happiness has really deskel-ated!
That's amazing, Ajimi!
It's still hard to understand you, though.
They're pretty good-pri.
You could use them for wanted posters-pri.
Now that you mention it!
Ajimi, you're with the police, aren't you?
You don't need to hide it from us.
You decided to not dress like a policewoman
so the perp wouldn't catch on, right?
Oh! That makes sense.
Come on, girls...
Did something happen?
Oh my, how terrible.
This is where the clue was found?
An eerie picture drawn on the ground...
This is the seventh.
Hey, Meganii!
Did something happen?
Be a good kid and don't imitate this.
Practical jokes are bad.
Rina, make it nice and clean.
Hang in there, Rina!
There have been other jokes like this one.
Infuriating!
Graffiti is ba-dechin!
So says someone who just drew on a wall-pri.
Bad-house of Medici!
Bad-da Vinci!
Listen when people talk-pri!
Bad-completely.
Plum-delicious.
It's possible that this is also
the work of Phantom Thief Genius.
Oh?
How so?
Well, it's just my intuition.
Don't you think Phantom Thief Genius
is the only person who would do this?
But why are they doing it?
Well, if we're able to catch them,
we might be able to figure that out.
Let's leave this to the police.
Now then, I must be off.
All right!
Let's go catch him!
Vinci?
Whether it was Phantom Thief Genius or not,
what's important is catching the culprit.
Right, Ajimi?
Important! Noble! Nobleman! Great man!
A great man is an admirable man-da Vinci!
To keep peace in PriPara!
Let's set out!
Let's Go!
Let's Gauguin!
Let's Go-ing My Way!
Let's Gogh!
Let it Go!
They're competing...
Let's da Vinci!
Derodero Derosaimu!
Meat buns are delicious!
This autumn appetite!
A suspicious individual has suddenly been found!
Apprehend her!
Devi?!
What hast thou done?!
I was just drawing my magic circle!
This is the autumn of summoning nefarious creatures!
Aroma may be impish, but she's not bad!
If you want to arrest Aroma,
you'll need to give Mikan three pizza buns!
Hey!
Is three pizza buns all I'm worth to thee?!
Just trying it out! Just trying it out!
Another suspicious individual spotted!
Arrest her!
Chanko was just drawing a sumo arena-chanko!
It's the autumn of sports-chanko!
Come on, Ajimi, pull it together.
Every single one of them have been innocent!
Will you really be able to catch the phantom thief like this?
Nyaha huh?
But why, oh why would Ajimi be trying
to catch the phantom thief-da Vinci?
Why would you?
You're with the police, aren't you, Ajimi?
Porisu?
Poorisu?
Porokku?
It looks like she's trying to figure something out.
But this seems to be the first time she's reacted to anything we've said.
Finally-pri?
Ajimi is not a member of the police-da Vinci!
Don't lie!
Ajimi is not so rousseau as to lie-DaVinci!
You're really not?
See.
So you're not undercover...
I'm uccello-ing you I'm not!
I'm not the police-da Vinci!
See? I told you so-pri.
No way!
Hmm.
No way...
Pushuu~
You're not?!
So you're not with the police.
Then I wonder who is with them.
Nyaha-da Vinci.
It doesn't really matter. Let's get going.
Henri-henri?
Hold Henri a Matisse-Da Vinci!
What is it?
You're not with the police, right?
Then it's okay.
It'll be impossible for us to catch this mischievous perpetrator in addition to the phantom thief-pri.
It is still too early to give up-da Vinci!
Ajimi!
Let's go go go to Christina's World-da Vinci!
Wait up!
This is the crime scene from earlier.
They sure did clean it up-pri.
Where is it? Where is it-da Vinci?
Ajimi, what are you doing?
Observing, observing!
What's important is observing-da Vinci!
Observing...
Meganii and Headmistress Ookanda
already cleaned up the area.
It's pointless. Pointless I say.
Make like the statue of David and stay put.
There's more here-da Vinci!
Hm?
Here!
Here-da Vinci! DaVinci!
Ah!
Spit it out.
What if it was poisoned?!
I was half choking-da Vinci.
But! But-claudeMonet!
It all makes sense-da Vinci!
Eh?!
This is...
...a sunflower seed-da Vinci!
A sunflower seed?!
What? So you're saying that the culprit is a hamster?
Isn't that a bit ridiculous?
Huh?
Eh?
Uh...?
Oh my?
Leonardo da Vinci!
Da-Da-Da Vinci! Da-Da-Da-Da Vinci!
I saw it-da Vinci!
Thank you, da Vinci-sama!
Da Vinci!
Bam!
Ajimi!
Ajimi.
What is it this time?
Huh?
Ah!
A hamster?!
Better yet, this!
This-da Vinci!
They're the sunflower seed shells-raphael.
Sunflower seeds, you say?
I get it! Sunflower seeds!
Which means...
This hamster! This hamster!
He! He is the Kokoschka Kandinsky culprit-da Vinci!
Uh-huh...
Well done, Ajimi.
Indeed. Those eerie pictures on the ground
were created by him.
Huh?!
Ta-da!
You solved the case that was as hard
to see through as opaque watercolour.
Exactly!
Ajimi done Raphael did it-da Vinci!
Huh?
What's the meaning of this?
Explain it properly-pri.
Sure thing.
This is the inspector that the PriPara Police dispatched upon my request.
Eh?!
Inspector?!
Him?!
Yes.
He's on the lookout for Phantom Thief Genius,
and has been staking out the place.
Which is when...
That means those eerie pictures...
Yes.
The sunflower seed shells just
happened to get scattered like that.
Eh?!
What the heck?!
Will an inspector like him be able to handle it?
He'll be fine.
Besides, I've also been patrolling.
Sir Ham also has other large issues he's responsible for.
As such, I thought I should find him a partner.
A partner?
If someone was able to figure out that
Sir Ham created those eerie pictures,
their insight and observation skills would be of great use to the police.
What do you mean-da Vinci?
Hm?
It's a police badge.
I can have it-da Vinci?
You've been recognized as his partner.
Please catch the phantom thief as
part of the Parajuku PriPara Police.
PriPara is a free place where power and money don't hold sway.
We must not succumb to anyone!
Okay! Okay!
Just leave it Chagall to Aji-me!
If you think Ajimi has what it takes
to join the police-da Vinci!
You got it. You can leave it all to Ajimi-da Vinci!
Are you sure?
I'm beyond worried-pri.
But that is a charm, isn't it?
Which means that he's also Ajimi's...
Manager?!
Ajimi's police and idol debut!
Congratulations!
What's this-da Vinci?
The new PriPass, the Cyalume Miracle Pact!
Like a palette, it's perfect for you who paints pictures.
Thank you, thank you, thanks a million-da Vinci!
Isn't that great, Ajimi?!
It's not fair, not fair at all that only Ajimi gets one!
Don't fret. All of you will receive
new PriPasses soon enough.
Additionally, Ajimi...
Yes-easel?
I also have a present for you.
What in the name of Raphael is it?
A new song!
I've warmed it up for you!
Good luck with your first concert!
Ajimi!
Ajimi, go, go!
Welcome back.
So an idol is making her debut today?
Yes.
Kiki Ajimi.
I wonder if she could be another princess?
An art idol, huh?
I wonder what kind of concert it'll be-kuma.
I can't wait to see!
DaVinci!
Making Drama Switch On!
Snip, snip!
It's done!
Cutout Plushy Kingdom!
Cyalume Change!
DaVinci!
Ajimi got blue; pop.
Happy heart!
Jumping, dancing, cheerful, blazing,
fun, heart-pounding debut concert!
Thank you so much-da Vinci!
A flower of a smile!
Ajiri wants to bloom even Michelangelo more-PicassoDaVinci!
That gave me a headache!
Th-That sure was something, but...
I wonder if she'll even be able
to catch Phantom Thief Genius...
Best not expect too much out of her-kuma.
Though, you did mention something
about her manager being a hamster, right-kuma?
Will the police be okay-usa?
Huh?!
Ah!
Sir Ham-usa!
Sir Ham-kuma!
W-What?
Sir Ham?
Everyone, lower your heads-usa!
Everyone, lower your heads-kuma!
This gentleman is...
...the legendary manager, Sir Ham!
Or his full name:
Hannibal Caesar Elizabeth Archimedes Newton Duke The Tougou Boss Yujiro Master of Mascots
Sir At The New Century We Are The World We Are The Sun Flower Friedrich
At The New Century We Are The World We Are The Sun Flower Friedrich
H A M Tarou The Great Golden Selime-usa!
H A M Tarou The Great Golden Selime-senpai-kuma!
What's that?
He has a great legacy-kuma!
For instance, he might be able to fit 256 sunflower seeds in his cheek pouch!
He might be a model for Hamony Land.
It's been said that he's been
around the world in his hamster wheel.
This is that Sir Ham-usa!
This is that Sir Ham-kuma!
Wow!
Yeah, wow...
Sir Ham, we are at your service-usa!
Sir Ham, we are at your service-kuma!
I've got a major headache.
Master Hibiki?
I'll take a break from watching PriPara TV.
Oh?
DaVinci!
She seems suspicious-da Vinci!
She's super flashy and gaudy! It's rather suspicious!
She seems like the phantom thief-da Vinci!
Investigate! Investigate! Inter interrogate!
Time to check into her-da Vinci!
Dear students,
I would like to introduce the
new art teacher we have appointed.
Ajimi?!
She's a teacher?!
She's older than us?!
Roger!
Yehellow!
I'm Kiki Ajimi.
I'm your art teacher from here on out-da Vinci!